http://www.modernity.se/privacy-policy/

Modernity’s Privacy Policy
This policy applies to information held about clients and prospective clients, suppliers, artists, contacts and all other persons about whom Modernity Stockholm AB holds information.
By “information”, we mean personal information about you that we collect, use, share and store.
In this policy, “we”, “us”, and “our” means Modernity Stockholm AB, a company registered in Sweden with No. 556662-6718, registered office Sibyllegatan 6, 114 42 Stockholm, Sweden, and “you” means the individual to whom the information relates.
What we collect
-	Your name
-	Your contact information such as your address, email address and telephone number
-	Your payment details/financial data i.e. your bank name, account number and sort code
-	Information related to your attendance of, and interest in, exhibitions, events and fairs
-	Information about you that you give us in person at our events and art fairs or by corresponding with us by phone, email, via social networks or otherwise
-	Information in relation to your purchase of our pieces or use of our services.
How we collect information about you
-	Collecting information you give to us when you purchase from us via email, phone, at a fair or at our gallery in Stockholm
-	Your written request to add you on our mailing list
-	Your information enquiries received by email or over the telephone.
What we do with the information we gather
We use your information to:
-	Provide information about our pieces and services to you
-	Keep you informed about pieces, artists and events that we think you may find interesting
-	Communicate with you
-	Comply with legal and regulatory obligations and for security to check your identity
Legal basis for processing
Our processing of your personal information is necessary
-	For the performance of contracts to which you will be a party to and in order to take steps at your request prior to you entering into those contracts
-	For the purposes of legitimate interests pursued by us
-	In order to comply with a legal obligation to which we are subject.
In relation to any processing of special categories of personal data, we will generally rely on obtaining specific consent from you at the time unless there is otherwise a legal requirement for us to process such information.
Legitimate interests
Where our processing is based on the legitimate interest grounds described above, those legitimate interests are:
-	Collecting personal information to provide you with a smooth and efficient client experience
-	To make sure you receive updated information on Modernity Stockholm AB’s business activities
-	To provide the services you have requested
-	Maintaining a record of your collection to ensure an efficient client experience
-	For our own marketing and research.
-
Sharing your information
Except as expressly set out in this policy, we will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
The personal information you provide to us may be shared with third companies or service providers if this is necessary to provide you with our pieces or services, respond to your enquiries or for any of the purposes described in this policy.
We may also share your personal information with law enforcement agencies, or governmental agencies or third parties if we are required by law to do so.
Transferring your information outside Sweden, Europe
Your personal information may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our service providers.
When we, or our permitted third parties, transfer your information outside the EEA, we or they will impose obligations on the recipients of that data to protect your information to the standard required in the EEA or otherwise require the recipient to subscribe to international frameworks intended to enable secure data sharing. In the case of transfers by us, we may also transfer your information where the transfer is to a country deemed to provide adequate protection of your information by the European Commission, or where you have consented to do the transfer.
Your rights
At any time, you have the right:
-	To request access to or a copy of any personal data which we hold about you
-	To rectification of your personal data, if you consider that the information we are holding is inaccurate
-	To ask us to delete your personal data, if you consider that we do not have the right to hold it
-	To withdraw consent to our processing of your personal data (to the extent such processing is based on previously obtained consent)
-	To ask us to stop or start sending you marketing messages as described below in the marketing section
-	To restrict processing of your personal data
-	To data portability (moving some of your personal data elsewhere) in certain circumstances
-	To object to your personal data being processed in certain circumstances
-	To not be subject to a decision based on automated processing and to have safeguards put in place if you are being profiled based on your personal data.
Any request from you for access to or a copy of your personal data must be in writing and we will endeavor to respond within a reasonable period and in any event within one month in compliance with data protection legislation. We will comply with our legal obligations as regarding your rights as a data subject.
We aim to ensure that the information we hold about you is accurate at all times. To assist us in ensuring that your information is up to date, do let us know if any of your personal details change at the following email address: info@modernity.se
Marketing
Where you are one of our clients or have otherwise agreed to be contacted for marketing we may use your personal information to send you information about events, exhibitions, art fairs and pieces. You can unsubscribe from receiving them at any time by emailing info@modernity.se with this request.
You also have the option of “unsubscribing” form our mailing list at any time thereby disabling any further such email or other communication from being sent to you by emailing info@modernity.se
We will action any opt out request from you without delay.
How long will we keep your information?
We will only keep information we collect about you for as long as required for the purposes set out above or as required to comply with any legal obligations to which we are subject. This will involve us periodically reviewing our files to check that information is accurate, up-to-date and still required.
Where we are permitted to send you direct marketing communications we may retain your contact information necessary for this purpose, for as long as you do not unsubscribe from receiving the same from us. If you opt out from marketing, we will retain your information to enable us to respect your wishes to not be contacted for marketing purposes.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Links to other sites
Our website may contain links to other sites, including via our social media buttons. While we try to link only to websites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other websites and a link does not constitute an endorsement of that website. Once you link to another website from our website you are subject to the terms and conditions of that website, including, but not limited to, its internet privacy policy and practices. Please check these policies before you submit any data to these websites.
Certain features of our site will allow for social networking. You should ensure when using these features that you do not submit any personal data that you do not want to be sent, collected or used by other users, such as profile details or email address.
Complaints
Questions, comments and requests regarding this policy are welcome and should be addressed to info@modernity.se
If you have any concerns about our use of your information, you also have the right (as a Swedish resident) to make a complaint to the Data Inspection Office, which regulates and supervises the use of personal data in Sweden:
Monday to Friday:
09.00–11.30 and 12.30–15.00
T: +46 8-657 61 00
datainspektionen@datainspektionen.se
Changes to this policy
Any changes we make to our policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our policy.
« Back
EnlargeDecrease
Close
Next »
Back «
Next »
